Finding aid for the Sam Manners papers, 1966-1988 LSC.2259
UCLA Library Special Collections
Sam Manners papers
1966-1988
UCLA Library Special Collections
LSC.2259
10.8 linear feet (2 boxes and 10 cartons)
Sam Manners was a television and motion picture producer with credits such as Dummy, Guyana Tragedy: The Story of Jim Jones, The Naked City, and Route 66. The bulk of the collection consists of bound scripts from Manners' television and motion picture projects. Also included are a small amount of photographs and biographical materials.
Conditions on Access
Portions of this collection, boxes 7 and 12, are restricted from access and requires advanced notice for use.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Gift of Kelly Manners; 2014.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9976857823606533
Biography/History
Savino Maneri, later changed to Sam Manners, was born March 29, 1921 in Cleveland, Ohio. Manners began his career as a production supervisor on the television series, The Adventures of Rin-Tin-Tin. He went on to become an associate producer, a production executive and second unit director on the series Naked City, and associate producer, executive in charge of production and second unit director on the series Route 66. Among his other television credits are the series Dundee and Cullhane, Petrocelli, and The Wild Wild West, and the television movies Dummy and Guyana Tragedy: The Story of Jim Jones, which were both Emmy nominated for outstanding special. Manners' motion picture credits include Cleopatra Jones, The Deadly Trackers, and Valdez is Coming, among others. Sam Manners died June 1, 2012.
Scope and Content
Collection consists of materials related to the career of television and motion picture producer Sam Manners. Included are bound television and motion picture scripts, photographs, and a scrapbook created by Manners. The majority of the scripts document Manners' television career including Adventures of Rin-Tin-Tin, Dummy, Dundee and the Cullhane, The Naked City, Route 66, Petrocelli, and The Wild Wild West among others. Motion picture projects represented include Cleopatra Jones, The Deadly Trackers, and Valdez is Coming, among others. A small number of scripts are authored by Manners. The small collection of photographs are professional and/or personal in nature. The scrapbook contains mostly clippings from magazines and newspapers and a small number of programs and photographs documenting Manners' career.
Organization and Arrangement
Arranged in the following series:
1. Biographical Information
2. Television Projects
3. Motion Picture Projects
4. Photographs.
Television producers and directors -- United States -- Archives.; Motion picture producers and directors -- United States -- Archives.; Manners, Sam -- Archives
- Biographical Information, undated; (Box 11)
  Scope and Content
  This series consists of a scrapbook titled, Savino Maneri: This is Your Life? By Sam Manners.
  - Savino Maneri: This is Your Life? by Sam Manners - scrapbook, ca. 1940s-1962 (Box 11)
    Mostly clippings from magazines and newspapers and a small number of programs and photographs documenting Manners' career.
- Television Projects, 1956-1981; (Boxes 1-10)
  This series consists of bound scripts documenting a variety of television series and TV movies in which Manners was involved. Additionally there are a small number of photographs. The television series scripts represent programs such as Dundee and Cullhane, The Naked City, Rin-Tin-Tin, Route 66, and The Wild Wild West, among others. Television movie scripts include Dummy, Hot Rod, and Pearl, among others. A small number of scripts were authored by Manners. The photographs are related to productions of Dummy, Pearl, and Route 66, among others. Notably absent are materials pertaining to Manner's Emmy nominated television movie Guyana Tragedy: The Story of Jim Jones. The series is arranged alphabetically by project title.
  Boxes 7 and 12 are restricted from access and requires advanced notice for use.
  - Adventures of Rin-Tin-Tin photograph of James Brown as Rip Masters, ca. 1958 (Box 11)
    James Brown.
  - Adventures of Rin-Tin-Tin: The Accusation - final draft script, 1958 Apr 23 (Box 1)
    Scope and Contents
    In bound volume labeled Rin-Tin-Tin Series V, Volume XIII, 1958-1959.
  - Angel Loves Nobody - script written by Sam Manners, 1973 Nov 1 (Box 9)
  - Archer: The Underground Man - final revised draft script, 1974 Feb 8 (Box 7)
    Conditions on Access
    Item is restricted and requires advance notice for use.
  - Barbary Coast - script, 1975 Feb 28 (Box 9)
  - Bearcats!: Dos Gringos - final draft script, 1971 Jun 28 (Box 7)
    In bound volume labeled Bearcats Series I, Volume I, 1971-1972.
  - Bearcats!: The Feathered Serpent - final draft script, 1971 Jul 12 (Box 7)
    General
  - Before and After - script, 1979 Jun 18 (Box 9)
  - Blondie: Sayonara, Dagwood - script, 1967 Nov 13 (Box 8)
  - Breaking Away: The American Dream - final script, 1980 Oct 14 (Box 10)
    In bound volume labeled Breaking Away Series I, Volume I, 1980-1981.
  - Breaking Away: King of the Quarry, 1980 Oct 8 (Box 10)
  - Breaking Away: Knowing Her... - revised final draft script, 1980 Oct 29 (Box 10)
  - [Deadly Trackers] photographs 3 items (Box 11)
    Manners, Richard Harris, and other unidentified individuals.
  - Divorce Wars - final draft script, 1981 July 28 (Box 12)
  - Dummy - final shooting script, 1978 Oct 19 (Box 9)
  - Dummy photographs (4 items), undated (Box 11)
    With Manners, Paul Servino, and other unidentified individuals.
  - Dundee and the Cullhane: The 1000 Feet Deep: Brief - script, 1967 Aug 30 (Box 6)
    In bound volume labeled Dundee and the Cullhane Series I, Volume III, 1967-1968.
  - Dundee and the Cullhane: The 3:10 To A Lynching: Brief - revised final draft script, 1967 Jul 25 (Box 6)
    In bound volume labeled Dundee and the Cullhane Series I, Volume II, 1967-1968.
  - Dundee and the Cullhane: The Cat in the Bag Brief - script, 1966 Nov 28 (Box 6)
    In bound volume labeled Dundee and the Cullhane Series I, Volume I, 1967-1968.
  - Dundee and the Cullhane: The Catch-A-Thief: Brief - final draft script, 1967 Jun 16 (Box 6)
  - Dundee and the Cullhane: The Dead Man's Brief - revised script, 1967 May 31 (Box 6)
  - Dundee and the Cullhane: The Duelist: Brief - final draft script, 1967 Aug 8 (Box 6)
  - Dundee and the Cullhane: The Jubilee Raid: Brief - 2nd revised final script, 1967 Jul 14 (Box 6)
  - Dundee and the Cullhane: The Las of the Buffalo Brief - revised script, 1967 May 12 (Box 6)
  - Dundee and the Cullhane: The Murderer Stallion: Brief - script, 1967 Aug 2 (Box 6)
  - Dundee and the Cullhane: Thy Brother's Keeper: Brief - script, 1967 Sep 18 (Box 6)
  - Dundee and the Cullhane: The Turn the Other Cheek Brief - final draft script, 1967 Jun 13 (Box 6)
  - Dundee and the Cullhane: The Vasquez Brief - script, 1967 Jun 26 (Box 6)
  - Dundee and the Cullhane: The Widow's Weeds: Brief - revised script, 1967 Sep 8 (Box 6)
  - From Russia with Sex - script, undated (Box 10)
  - Grumman, Missing Persons - script written by Sam Manners and John Montgomery, 1977 Mar 31 (Box 9)
  - Hawaii Five-O: Once Upon a Time - first draft script, 1968 Aug 27 (Box 8)
  - Hot Rod - final draft script, 1979 Mar 2 (Box 9)
  - [Hot Rod] photographs of Manners (2 items), undated (Box 11)
  - Lassiter: Tonight We Make Them Cry - final script, 1966 Nov 1 (Box 8)
  - The Mad Messiah: Part I - script, 1979 Oct 31 (Box 12)
    In binding labeled The Mad Messiah, 1979.
  - The Mad Messiah: Part II - script, 1979 Oct 31 (Box 12)
  - Mongo's Back in Town - script, ca. 1971 Sep (Box 7)
  - The Naked City photographs (Box 11)
    Sam Manners, Horace McMahon, and unidentified crew.
  - The Naked City: And A Merry Christmas to the Force on Patrol - final draft teleplay, 1958 Oct 15 (Box 1)
    In bound volume labeled Naked City Series I, Volume II, 1958-1959.
  - The Naked City: Alive and Still a Second Lieutenant - script, 1963 Feb 21 (Box 4)
    In bound volume labeled Naked City Series IV, Volume XIII, 1962-1963.
  - The Naked City: The Apple Falls Not Far From the Tree - script, 1963 Jan 7 (Box 4)
  - The Naked City: Baker's Dozen - first draft teleplay, 1959 Feb 18 (Box 2)
    In bound volume labeled Naked City Series I, Volume III, 1958-1959.
  - The Naked City: Barefoot on a Bed of Coals - final draft screenplay, 1963 May 3 (Box 3)
    In bound volume labeled Naked City Series IV, Volume XIV, 1962-1963.
  - The Naked City: Belvedere Tower - revised final draft script, 1958 Sep 8 (Box 1)
    In bound volume labeled Naked City Series I, Volume I, 1958-1959.
  - The Naked City: Beyond This Place There Be Dragons - script, 1963 Jan 15 (Box 4)
  - The Naked City: The Bird Guard - final draft teleplay, 1958 Jul 21 (Box 1)
  - The Naked City: The Bloodhounds - first draft teleplay, 1959 Apr 10 (Box 2)
  - The Naked City: Bridge Party - script, no date (Box 2)
    In bound volume labeled Naked City Series III, Volume VI, 1961-1962.
  - The Naked City: Bringing Far Places Together - script, 1962 Jan 31 (Box 4)
  - The Naked City: The Bumper - final draft teleplay, 1959 Jan 17 (Box 1)
  - The Naked City: Burst of Passion- first draft teleplay, 1958 Nov 12 (Box 1)
  - The Naked City: Button in a Haystack - script, 1960 Aug 1 (Box 2)
    In bound volume labeled Naked City Series II, Volume I, 1960-1961.
  - The Naked City: And By the Sweat of Thy Brow - script, ca. 1962 Aug 12 (Box 3)
    In bound volume labeled Naked City Series IV, Volume X1, 1962-1963.
  - The Naked City: The Canvas Bullet - first draft teleplay, 1959 May 4 (Box 2)
  - The Naked City: Carrier - final draft screenplay, 1963 Mar 22 (Box 3)
  - The Naked City: A Case Study of Two Savages - script, ca. 1962 Jan 16 (Box 3)
    In bound volume labeled Naked City Series III, Volume VIII, 1961-1962.
  - The Naked City: Color Schemes Like Never Before - final draft screenplay, 1963 Apr 4 (Box 3)
  - The Naked City: The Contract - script, ca. 1961 Dec 27 (Box 3)
  - The Naked City: A Corpse Ran Down Mulberry Street" - script, no date (Box 2)
  - The Naked City: Daughter, Am I In My Father's House? - script, ca. 1962 Jun 6 (Box 3)
  - The Naked City: The Day the Island Almost Sank - final draft screenplay, 1961 May 18 (Box 2)
    In bound volume labeled Naked City Series II, Volume V, 1960-1961.
  - The Naked City: Dead on the Field of Honor! - script, no date (Box 2)
  - The Naked City: A Death of Princess - script, no date (Box 2)
  - The Naked City: Debt of Honor - second draft script, 1960 Jul 26 (Box 2)
  - The Naked City: Dust Devil on a Quiet Street - script, 1962 Nov 9 (Box 3)
    In bound volume labeled Naked City Series IV, Volume XII, 1962-1963.
  - The Naked City: Even Crows Sing Good - final draft teleplay, 1958 Nov 6 (Box 1)
  - The Naked City: The Explosive Heart - revised final draft teleplay, 1958 Oct 21 (Box 1)
  - The Naked City: The Face of the Enemy - script, ca. 1961 (Box 2)
    In bound volume labeled Naked City Series III, Volume VII, 1961-1962.
  - The Naked City: Fallen Star - final draft script, 1959 Feb 12 (Box 2)
  - The Naked City: The Fingers of Henri Tourelle - script, no date (Box 2)
  - The Naked City: Fire Island - first draft teleplay, 1959 Jan 7 (Box 1)
  - The Naked City: Four Sweet Corners - first draft teleplay, 1959 Mar 11 (Box 2)
  - The Naked City: Golden Lads and Girls - final draft screenplay, 1963 Apr 24 (Box 3)
  - The Naked City: Goodbye Mama, Hello Auntie Maud - script, ca. 1962 May 31 (Box 3)
    In bound volume labeled Naked City Series III, Volume X, 1961-1962.
  - The Naked City: Goodbye My Lady Love - final draft teleplay, 1958 Dec 15 (Box 1)
  - The Naked City: Her Life in Moving Pictures - script, 1962 Dec 18 (Box 3)
  - The Naked City: Hey, Teach..! - first draft teleplay, 1958 Dec 15 (Box 1)
  - The Naked City: The Highest of Prizes - script, 1963 (Box 4)
    With some pages titled Vengeance is Mine, Saith the Lord.
  - The Naked City: Hold For Gloria Christmas - script, ca. 1962 Jul 18 (Box 3)
  - The Naked City: A Horse Has a Big Head -- Let Him Worry - script, 1962 Oct 15 (Box 3)
  - The Naked City: The Hot Minerva - revised script, 1961 Jun 1 (Box 2)
  - The Naked City: Howard Running Bear is a Turtle - revised final draft script, 1963 Mar 6 (Box 3)
  - The Naked City: Idylls of a Running Back - script, ca. 1962 Sep 7 (Box 3)
  - The Naked City: And If Any Are Frozen Warm Them - script, ca. 1962 Apr 17 (Box 3)
  - The Naked City: Kill Me While I'm Young So I Can Die Happy! - script, ca. 1962 Sep 26 (Box 3)
  - The Naked City: King Stanislaus and the Knights of the Round Stable - script, 1962 Nov 20 (Box 3)
  - The Naked City: A Kettle of Precious Fish - first draft screenplay, 1961 May 3 (Box 2)
  - The Naked City: The King of Venus Will Take Care of You - script, ca. 1962 May 9 (Box 3)
  - The Naked City: Lady Bug, Lady Bug... - second revised final draft script, 1958 Oct 13 (Box 1)
  - The Naked City: Let Me Die Before I Wake - script, ca. 1962 Jan 29 (Box 3)
  - The Naked City: Line of Duty - final draft script, 1958 Jul 31 (Box 1)
  - The Naked City: Make It Fifty Dollars and Add Love to Nona - script, 1962 Oct 26 (Box 3)
  - The Naked City: Man Without a Skin - script, 1963 Jan 18 (Box 4)
  - The Naked City: The Manhole - revised final draft teleplay, 1958 Nov 8 (Box 1)
  - The Naked City: Memory of a Red Trolley Car - script, ca. 1962 May 24 (Box 3)
  - The Naked City: The Multiplicity of Herbert Konish - script, ca. 1962 May 3 (Box 3)
  - The Naked City: New York to L.A. - script, no date (Box 2)
  - The Naked City: Nickel Ride - final draft script, 1958 Jun 16 (Box 1)
  - The Naked City: The Night the Saints Lost Their Halos - script, ca.1961 December 15 (Box 3)
  - The Naked City: No More Rumbles - revised final draft script, 1958 Aug 13 (Box 1)
  - The Naked City: No Naked Ladies in Front of Giovanni's House! - final draft screenplay, 1963 Mar 15 (Box 3)
  - The Naked City: Nothing But the Truth - first draft teleplay, 1959 Feb 9 (Box 2)
  - The Naked City: On the Battlefront: Every Minute is Important - script, 1963 Mar 12 (Box 4)
  - The Naked City: One of the Most Important Men in the Whole World - script, ca. 1962 Jan 8 (Box 3)
  - The Naked City: One, Two, Three, Rita Rakahowski - final draft screenplay, 1963 Apr 17 (Box 3)
  - The Naked City: One to Get Lost - second revised final draft script, 1958 Dec 1 (Box 1)
  - The Naked City: Ooftus Goofus - script, ca. 1961 (Box 2)
  - The Naked City: The Other Face of Goodness - revised final draft script, 1958 Jul 12 (Box 1)
  - The Naked City: The Pedigree Sheet - first draft screenplay, 1960 Jun 21 (Box 2)
  - The Naked City: A Piece of the Action - first draft script, 1959 Apr 2 (Box 2)
  - The Naked City: Portrait of a Painter - script, ca. 1961 Nov 29 (Box 3)
  - The Naked City: Prime of Life - script, 1962 Nov 16 (Box 3)
  - The Naked City: Rebirth - script, 1959 Mar 6 (Box 2)
  - The Naked City: Requiem for a Sunday Afternoon - script, ca. 1961 (Box 2)
  - The Naked City: Robin Hood and Clarence Darrow, They Went Out With the Bow and Arrow - script, 1932 Dec 20 (Box 3)
  - The Naked City: A Running of Bulls - first draft script, 1959 Jan 27 (Box 1)
  - The Naked City: The Rydecker Case - script, ca. 1962 May 18 (Box 3)
  - The Naked City: The S.S. American Dream - final draft screenplay, 1963 Apr 15 (Box 3)
  - The Naked City: The Sandman - first draft script, 1959 Mar 16 (Box 2)
  - The Naked City: Saw My Baby There - final draft teleplay, 1959 Apr 24 (Box 2)
  - The Naked City: The Scorpion Sting - first draft teleplay, 1959 Apr 16 (Box 2)
  - The Naked City: The Shield - first draft teleplay, 1958 Dec 3 (Box 1)
  - The Naked City: Show Me the Way to Go Home - script, ca. 1961 (Box 2)
  - The Naked City: Sidewalk Fisherman - final draft script, 1958 Jul 3 (Box 1)
  - The Naked City: Spectre of the Rose Street Gang - script, 1962 Nov 30 (Box 3)
  - The Naked City: Stakeout - final draft script, 1958 Aug 28 (Box 1)
  - The Naked City: Stop the Parade! A Baby is Crying! - script, 1963 Mar 1 (Box 4)
  - The Naked City: Strike a Statue - script, ca. 1962 Apr 24 (Box 3)
  - The Naked City: Susquehanna 7-8367 - revised final draft script, 1958 Sep 20 (Box 1)
  - The Naked City: A Swedish Jewel - script, no date (Box 2)
  - The Naked City: Sweet Prince of Delancey Street - first draft screenplay, 1961 May 13 (Box 2)
  - The Naked City: Take and Put - first draft screenplay, 1961 May 24 (Box 2)
  - The Naked City: Take Off Your Hat When a Funeral Passes - script, no date (Box 2)
  - The Naked City: Ten Cent Dreams first draft teleplay, 1959 Jan 12 (Box 1)
  - The Naked City: Ticker Tape - final draft script, 1958 Sep 15 (Box 1)
  - The Naked City: Torment Him Much and Hold Him Long - script, ca. 1962 Sep 12 (Box 3)
  - The Naked City: The Tragic Success of Alfred Tiloff - script, ca. 1961 (Box 2)
  - The Naked City: Turn of Events - revised final draft script, 1959 Mar 24 (Box 2)
  - The Naked City: The Violent Circle - final draft script, 1958 Jun 23 (Box 1)
  - The Naked City: The Virtues of Madame Douvay - script, ca. 1962 Aug 17 (Box 3)
  - The Naked City: Which is Joseph Creeley? - script, ca. 1961 (Box 2)
  - The Naked City: A Wood of Thorns - first draft teleplay, 1959 May 10 (Box 2)
  - Pearl: Episode I - script, 1978 Apr (Box 9)
    In binding labeled Pearl, 1978.
  - Pearl: Episode II - script, 1978 Apr (Box 9)
  - Pearl: Episode III - script, 1978 Apr (Box 9)
  - [Pearl] photographs (9 items), undated (Box 11)
    Sam Manners, Adam Arkin, Robert Wagner, Dennis Weaver, Natalie Wood, and other unidentified individuals.
  - The Perils of Pauline: Oh the Tragedy of it All - final draft teleplay, 1965 Nov 8 (Box 8)
  - [Petrocelli?] photographs (Box 11)
    With Manners, Barry Newman, Albert Salmi and other unidentified individuals at an event.
  - Petrocelli - revised shooting script for Movie of the Week, 1973 Dec 31 (Box 7)
  - Petrocelli: An Act of Love - first draft script, 1974 Sep 17 (Box 7)
    In bound volume labeled Petrocelli Series I, Volume II, 1974-1975.
  - Petrocelli: Concerto in Death Major - second draft script, 1974 Aug 15 (Box 7)
    In bound volume labeled Petrocelli Series I, Volume I, 1974-1975.
  - Petrocelli: Counterploy - final draft script, 1974 Oct 14 (Box 7)
    In bound volume labeled Petrocelli Series I, Volume III, 1974-1975.
  - Petrocelli: A Covenant With Evil - final draft script, 1974 Oct 28 (Box 7)
  - Petrocelli: Death in High Places - second draft script, 1974 Aug 28 (Box 7)
  - Petrocelli: Death in Small Doses - revised script, 1974 Jul 10 (Box 7)
    In bound volume labeled Petrocelli Series I, Volume 1, 1974-1975.
  - Petrocelli: The Double Negative - fourth draft script, 1974 Sep 10 (Box 7)
  - Petrocelli: Edge of Evil - final draft script, 1974 Aug 26 (Box 7)
  - Petrocelli: For the Love of Pete - script written by Sam Manners, 1975 Aug 5 (Box 8)
  - Petrocelli: Four the Hard Way - final draft script, 1974 Oct 1 (Box 7)
  - Petrocelli: The Golden Cage - final draft script, 1974 Aug 5 (Box 7)
  - Petrocelli: The Kidnapping - second draft script, 1974 Nov 13 (Box 7)
  - Petrocelli: A Life for a Life - second revised final script, 1974 Jul 26 (Box 7)
  - Petrocelli: Mirror, Mirror on the Wall - first draft script, 1974 Sep 25 (Box 7)
  - Petrocelli: Music to Die By - script, 1974 Jul 15 (Box 7)
  - Petrocelli: Once Upon a Victim - final draft script, 1974 Nov 5 (Box 7)
  - Petrocelli: A Very Lonely Lady - final draft script, 1974 Oct 22 (Box 7)
  - Powderkeg - script, 1971 Jan 7 (Box 8)
  - Powderkeg: The Devil Wears Armor - final draft script, 1971 June 3 (Box 7)
    In binding labeled Bearcats Series I, Volume I, 1971-1972.
  - Powderkeg: Ground Loop at Spanish Wells - final draft script, 1971 June 10 (Box 7)
  - The Pride of Jesse Hallam - final shooting script, 1980 Sep 22 (Box 9)
  - The Red Pony - final shooting script, 1972 Aug 7 (Box 8)
  - The Red Pony photographs (2 items on paper print outs), undated (Box 11)
    Sam Manners, Henry Fonda, and Maureen O'Hara.
  - Rescue 8: 3 Mile Bomb - final draft script, 1959 Jul 2 (Box 8)
    In bound volume labeled Rescue 8 Series II, Volume IV, 1959-1960.
  - Rescue 8: Dangerous Salvage - final draft script, 1959 Jul 15 (Box 8)
  - Rescue 8: Fools Gold - final draft script, 1959 May 25 (Box 8)
  - Rescue 8: Forced Landing, 1959 May 20 (Box 8)
  - Rescue 8: Not for Glory - final draft script, 1959 Jul 20 (Box 8)
  - Rescue 8: Paid in Full - final draft script, 1959 Jun 3 (Box 8)
  - Rescue 8: Rock Prison - final draft script, 1959 Jun 15 (Box 8)
  - Rescue 8: Suitcase Fireman - final draft script, 1959 Jun 16 (Box 8)
  - Adventures of Rin-Tin-Tin: The Failure - final draft script, 1958 Apr 22 (Box 1)
  - Adventures of Rin-Tin-Tin: The Foot Soldier - final draft script, 1957 Aug 21 (Box 1)
    In bound volume labeled Rin-Tin-Tin Series IV, Volume XI, 1957-1958.
  - Adventures of Rin-Tin-Tin: The General's Daughter - final draft script, 1957 Nov 26 (Box 1)
  - Adventures of Rin-Tin-Tin: Gold Fever - final draft script, 1957 Nov 6 (Box 1)
  - Adventures of Rin-Tin-Tin: The Hunted - final draft script, 1957 Aug 30 (Box 1)
  - Adventures of Rin-Tin-Tin: Major Mockingbird - final draft script, 1958 Apr 24 (Box 1)
  - Adventures of Rin-Tin-Tin: The Misfit Marshall - final draft script, 1958 Mar 31 (Box 1)
  - Adventures of Rin-Tin-Tin: The New C.O. - final draft script, 1957 Oct 18 (Box 1)
  - Adventures of Rin-Tin-Tin: Pillajohn's Progress - final draft script, 1958 Apr 18 (Box 1)
  - Adventures of Rin-Tin-Tin: Pritikin's Predicament - final draft script, 1957 Oct 16 (Box 1)
  - Adventures of Rin-Tin-Tin: River Chase - final draft script, 1956 Apr 30 (Box 1)
  - Adventures of Rin-Tin-Tin: The Royal Recruit - final draft script, 1958 Apr 1 (Box 1)
  - Adventures of Rin-Tin-Tin: Running Horse - final draft script, 1957 Nov 7 (Box 1)
  - Adventures of Rin-Tin-Tin: Rusty's Opportunity - final draft script, 1957 Nov 22 (Box 1)
  - Adventures of Rin-Tin-Tin: Rusty's Remedy - final draft script, 1957 Oct 8 (Box 1)
  - Adventures of Rin-Tin-Tin: Sorrowful Joe's Policy - final draft script, 1957 Nov 4 (Box 1)
  - Adventures of Rin-Tin-Tin: Tomahawk Tubbs - final draft script, 1957 Oct 1 (Box 1)
  - Adventures of Rin-Tin-Tin: White Chief - final draft script, 1957 Sep 6 (Box 1)
  - Route 66 photographs (2 items) (Box 11)
    Sam Manners, Martin Milner, George Maharis and other unidentified individuals.
  - Route 66: ...And the Cat Jumped Over the Moon - script, 1961 Nov 27 (Box 4)
    In bound volume labeled Route 66 Series II, Volume VIII, 1961-1962.
  - Route 66: ...Shall Forfeit his Dog and Ten Shillings to the King - script, 1963 Jan 3 (Box 5)
    In bound volume labeled Route 66 Series III, Volume XIII, 1962-1963.
  - Route 66: 93 Per Cent in Smiling, 1963 Nov 29 (Box 5)
    In bound volume labeled Route 66 Series VI, Volume XVI, 1963-1964.
  - Route 66: 1800 Days to Justice - script, 1961 Dec 28 (Box 4)
  - Route 66: Across Walnuts and Wine - final draft screenplay, 1962 Jul 12 (Box 5)
    In bound volume labeled Route 66 Series III, Volume XI, 1962-1963.
  - Route 66: Aren't You Surprised to See Me? - script, 1962 Jan 29 (Box 4)
  - Route 66: Between Hello and Goodbye - script, no date (Box 4)
    In bound volume labeled Route 66 Series II, Volume X, 1961-1962.
  - Route 66: Blues for the Left Foot - script, 1962 Feb 19 (Box 4)
    In bound volume labeled Route 66 Series II, Volume IX, 1961-1962.
  - Route 66: A Bridge Across Five Days - script, 1961 Oct 25 (Box 4)
    In bound volume labeled Route 66 Series II, Volume VII, 1961-1962.
  - Route 66: A Bunch of Lonely Pagliaccis - script, 1962 Dec 13 (Box 5)
  - Route 66: Build Your Houses With Their Backs to the Sea - final draft screenplay, 1963 Aug 7 (Box 5)
    In bound volume labeled Route 66 Series VI, Volume XV, 1963-1964.